var quizArray = [
  {
    question: "What colour is the JS logo?",
    choices: ["Yellow", "Blue", "Green", "Red"],
    answer: "Yellow",
  },
  {
    question: "When was JavaScript invented?",
    choices: ["1985", "1995", "2005", "2015"],
    answer: "1995",
  },
  {
    question: "A javaScript file has which extension?",
    choices: [".css", ".xml", ".html", ".js"],
    answer: ".js",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following displays a message and allows the user to type input?",
    choices: ["alert()", "prompt()", "confirm()", "msg()"],
    answer: "prompt()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I need to display something on the console in JavaScript. Which of the following do I need?",
    choices: ["console.log", "print", "display", "show"],
    answer: "console.log",
  },
  {
    question: "Which element links a javaScript file linked to a html file?",
    choices: ["js", "connect", "script", "link"],
    answer: "script",
  },
  {
    question: "var myNumbers = [1, 2, 3]\nmyNumbers an example of what?",
    choices: ["boolean", "method", "array", "object"],
    answer: "array",
  },
  {
    question: "What type of data structure uses key, value pairs?",
    choices: ["variable", "object", "array", "boolean"],
    answer: "object",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How do you repeat the same block of code, in multiple places, with javaScript? ?",
    choices: ["A data type", "An array", "A function", "An element"],
    answer: "A function",
  },
  {
    question: "jquery is a type of what?",
    choices: ["libary", "boolean", "expression", "function"],
    answer: "libary",
  },
];
